VBA Developer - UiPath Developer. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for Robot. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including Python, Visual Basic in Application, MySQL, and Uipath - Studio. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

NEO NGUYEN (DUY MINH NGUYEN)

Phone:

(+1) 647-713-1737

E-Mail:

neonguyen.ca@gmail.com

Skill Highlights

- Logical thinking
- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Languages

English Vietnamese

Experience

2 years - Freelance experience:

06/2020 to 07/2022

- Cooperate with customers to create a friendly and easy working environment.
- Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflows.
- Independently complete robot programming and development tasks for customers with the highest efficiency in the shortest time.
- Perform quality assurance tests to uncover errors and optimize usability.

7 years - Maths High School Teacher

09/2020 to 06/2017

Education

Bachelor: Mathematics Teacher Education

9/2006 to 9/2010

Ho Chi Minh University of Education - Viet Nam

Diploma: Computer Systems Technician
George Brown College - Canada

1/2018 to 5/2019

Certifications

Programming Languages: Python, Visual Basic in Application, MySQL, and Uipath - Studio

References

References available on request

Link

VBA in Excel – youtube link:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Alm8T32bJ_c https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xc-QjCArtMg